<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="style-scss/info.css"?>
<SECTION xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="note.xsd">
<GOLF>  
<NAME>Tournaments</NAME>
<INFO>
The major men's professional tournaments include the four major tournaments: The Masters Tournament, US Open, The Open Championship and the PGA Championship.

On October 9, 2009, at the 121st session of the IOC in Copenhagen, by 63 votes against 27[23], it was decided to include golf in the program of the 2016 Olympic Games in Rio de Janeiro[24]. Briton Justin Rose and Korean Park In Bi became Olympic champions in golf in 2016.
</INFO>
</GOLF>
<GOLF>
<NAME>Golf in space</NAME>
<INFO>
Astronaut Alan Shepard on the surface of the Moon during the Apollo 14 expedition in 1971 struck the first ball with a club in space.[25] The first time he discovered he missed the ball with a stick, but the second time, due to the weak lunar gravity and the Earth's atmosphere, the ball flew several kilometers.



A golf ball, which is space debris, is inaccessible to the ISS and, having entered the dense layers of the atmosphere, burned out. Just in case, Mikhail Tyurin had three balls at his disposal.
</INFO>
</GOLF>
<GOLF>
<NAME>Sticks</NAME>
<INFO>
Iron (eng. Iron) - a lighter stick with a spade-shaped head for aiming the ball at shorter distances. The angle of inclination of the impact plane is from 15째 to 45째. The sticks are numbered. A larger number allows you to send the ball at a greater angle to the horizon for a shorter distance. Impact distance from 70 to 150 meters.
    Wedges (eng. Wedge) - differ from iron even in a larger angle of the hitting surface (45 째 -64 째) and are needed to knock out the ball with a canopy, for example, from sand (Sand Wedge) or grass (Chipping Wedge) for a short distance.
    Putter (eng. Putter) - a stick with a light L-shaped head for playing on the green and applying stalemates - rolling strokes with which the ball rolls into the hole.
</INFO>
</GOLF>
<GOLF>
<NAME>balls</NAME>
<INFO>
The surface of an ordinary golf ball is covered with pits - dimples (dimples) (so that the ball better "holds" the direction in which it was hit)

Air is trapped in the pits and an invisible shell is formed, which:

    reduces the vibrations of the ball during flight,
    enhances the lifting effect when hitting the ball with a twist,
    improves its aerodynamic properties and allows the ball to fly further,
</INFO>
</GOLF>
<GOLF>
<NAME>Golf course</NAME>
<INFO>
The golf course consists of a series of holes, each of which has its own starting ground (Eng. Teeing ground). The starting area is marked with two marks showing the permissible boundaries of the zone where a ball peg (eng. Tee) can be installed. Also part of the site are a smooth field and an uneven field (Fairway and rough (English)) and other obstacles (English Hazard (golf)). The final part of the site is a hole, which, for the possibility of orientation, is marked in some way (usually with a flag). The hole is located on a special lawn "green" (Putting green (English)), where the height of the grass is minimal. In other places, the height of the grass may be very different in order to make it difficult to pass the site.
</INFO>
</GOLF>
<GOLF>
<NAME>Terms</NAME>
<INFO>
Green - (English green - "green lawn") a rounded part of the golf course with the shortest cut grass, where the hole itself is located [17].
Fairway - (English fairway - "central alley with smoothly cut grass") is a relatively flat part of the field, the grass on which is of medium length; occupies most of the field[17].
Rough - patches of tall grass that border the fairway and green[17].
A putt is a light shot played on the green, the main purpose of which is to roll the ball into the hole.
</INFO>
</GOLF>
</SECTION>